websitescale.com 2015-06-03

# Privacy Policy - Websitescale.com

If you need any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by navigating contact us page in the main menu   
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which websitescale.com collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users of our website. This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by websitescale.com. We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information. www.websitescale.com does not use cookies.   
If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to websitescale.com and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. Websitescale.com has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications. By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
